all right everyone John Kirika wrote an
article a couple of days ago with
regards to Julian Assange and the fact
that in his opinion it would be
impossible for Assange to get a fair
trial that is essentially if charges are
brought against him if the Ecuadorian
government does not shelter him if the
UK's government does indeed extradite
him to the US he will be put in prison
he'll basically rot in a Cell which is
kind of what he's doing now anyway a
cell with a smaller window and without a
comfy bed and spend the rest of his life
there under lock and key probably
without you know more than limited
access to the outside world like don't
you think there'd be [__] punitive
punishment and here's what you should
care about Jon Kirikou things really
great example during the middle of the
Obama administration and not many people
remember this via they think that Trump
attacks the press Barack Obama
personally oversaw the expansion of the
surveillance state to include trying to
head on after any journalist that was
reporting on information that was
classified they did this he was
conducting active surveillance for years
on a number of AP journalists when this
was found out people were enraged for a
while and they very quickly didn't care
anymore
I wonder why the legacy media shut up
was that the character was it the stick
that the DOJ came after them with John
Kirikou was a CIA agent years ago and he
gave an interview on NBC where he
discussed some of the finer points of
some waterboarding that had happened a
few you know cases of torture or
enhanced interrogation techniques prior
administration a belief at the time or
early Obama era and originally the CIA
and all these groups didn't really care
about it they're like yeah well he
didn't violate any rules he's just you
know talking informally in this
investigation then years later they said
oh yeah by the way he'd be violated you
know multiple laws we're gonna put him
in prison for 30 months so they held him
for two and a half years based on I
think five or six different charges they
found him guilty and I can't recall
exactly what they got him on
I think lying under I think he was lying
to investigators that was I think one
charge supposedly he was doing that
three counts of like classic food the
improper use of classified info or
something so they threw him in prison
this was the Obama era Obama supposedly
the great glowing messiah of the modern
liberal movement headhunted after
journalists he spied on them
he massively expanded the surveillance
state and then he played dumb and
pretended that he himself wasn't
involved in the decision-making process
with regards to the mass expansion of
NSA activities he stood in the way
repeatedly of any attempt to reform
these and he had run on a platform of
trying to undo damage towards
journalists and the surveillance state
and the police state sort of [__] of
the Bush era that is the way he
campaigner Obama was very much for the
First Amendment every possible respect
great reverence in in a solemn and grave
manner as a president should he looks at
the Fourth Amendment sheds a single tear
while Eagles sit behind him and spread
their wings you know gloriously backlit
by the Rising Sun rising over this great
libertarian land in reality though he
was really a corporate crook that gave
hundreds of billions of dollars to
private entities [__] around with the
economy on a grand scale and that pharma
companies design our health care laws
for some reason the modern liberals like
him I guarantee 20 30 years from now
they're gonna throw him under the bus
the same way they did Clinton based on
his his aberrant his own problems like
oh yeah that tough-on-crime stuff was
kind of bad for us oh yeah what about
that time that Bubba bill probably
sexually assaulted people no not Monica
Lewinsky the other three or four
examples every year of wanita Broderick
so I wonder why Kiera cow would think of
this oh and uh care about this yes I
happen to agree with him there's no way
Assange gets a fair trial here's the
problem when people who are well-meaning
they're saying oh well they just want to
bring us on track they just want to
charge you and put him on trial like
he'll get his day in court it'll get a
fair trial no he won't
are you [__] insane he's Julian
Assange and the thing is he has done it
I guaranteed and demonstrably
objectively speaking he has done nothing
that hasn't been done by the New York
Times and CNN and Fox and Breitbart and
Drudge every other major media firm in
the country of various times the only
difference is that because there's been
no scrutiny there's been no active
attempt to prosecute them you're telling
me Jay to all of the left wingers that
hate us on so much you're telling me you
want to hand the Trump administration
that you think
hiss fascistic the ability to prosecute
journalists and corporate media outlets
that's what you're saying to me he's
heads WikiLeaks he's basically the
spiritual head at this point the
charismatic figure head that has little
connection anymore with his own former
group WikiLeaks spent years dumping both
classified and rudimentary confidential
material on corporations on governments
and so forth
this is done by investigative
journalists in other respects all the
time what what did Ronan Farrow do with
regards to Weinstein it was
investigative journalism into otherwise
confidential aspects of a man's life and
they tried to suppress him by the way
yes they were afraid of getting sued for
defamation probably they were afraid of
a protracted battle with this
billionaire a political donor I wonder
why why do you think they had to
undercut him by creating the me to move
them in the first place
he have to weaken the foundation to take
the castle doom it's called a sapper
learn to learn a little bit of military
strategy you'll know a lot more about
politics too here's the thing Kiera cow
was abused by the Obama administration I
would say this my hope is that the Trump
administration will do what the Obama
administration was originally hired to
do and actually reform this the things
that are happening when Trump alludes to
the deep state is he not alluding to the
same sort of entrenched police state
loving censorship loving miscreant
establishment Arian [__] that Obama
ran against of course he is against war
and and surveillance and all of the bad
things in life but the Liberals have
been so mind-fucked at this point by the
post Obama era spin cycle that they
actually believe that Trump is the
treasonous one if he you know it stands
for journalism it's terrible it's a
violation of the First Amendment to
insult someone on Twitter but it has
it's not a violation of multi-billion
dollar companies that take tax subsidies
deep platform people entirely it's not a
violation of the rights of the press nor
a violation of the right to privacy nor
a violation of the basic fundamental
substance of journalism itself in an
ethical framework if Julian Assange gets
thrown in the gulag for the rest of his
life on tron ultimately trumped-up
charges that's not an attack on the
First Amendment the New York Times has
more sense than that they came out with
an art
the other day basically saying what pure
cows saying nobody can't get a fair
trial this would be an attack on the
press it shouldn't be done now
ultimately I have no doubt if the Obama
admin had suggested the same thing they
would have gone along with they would
they would have healed they would have
bowed before him and they would have
been been good little thought slaves
they wouldn't have dared take on Obama I
think the one good thing about the fact
that Trump has less support is that it
does make it possible for people to
decide against the government at large
and an abusive sense it is possible for
that to happen because as popularity
happens below now I would prefer to
trust Trump because I don't know yet
where he stands he seems to have leaned
more towards not wanting to charge a saw
and not really thinking that he broke
any laws I agree with that by the way
but he needs to come out and say it
plain I want to hear Trump give a speech
on the subject or at least allude to it
I want journalists to actually didn't
investigate his views on this and say
what do you think yes or no a son should
be extradited here to hold tribal to
stand trial I want to hear a plain yes
or no no no lawyers speak no politicians
spin [__] yes or no that's what I
want to hear from Trump and I want to
hear from each legacy media outlet the
New York Times that I have very little
respect for in all honesty in their
defense has come out and essentially
warned it would be a bad thing if
Assange we're charged then again at the
same time it's not too much defense of
them that I have and I'll tell you why
because they're not coming out and
saying and also he should be free and
clear and he should be able to leave the
embassy and not be [__] locked up
without any internet privileges you are
already ultimately holding the man in
jail he's your fellow journalist you
supposedly are journalists you should
defend him you should argue that the
nation of Ecuador should say we're not
gonna extradite the UK should an extra
night he should be free and clear to go
Sweden our teacher already made [__]
charges of sex assault against him that
turned out to be full of [__] he's
already but he's already had people say
he's treasonous he commits espionage he
does terrible things all he does is
publish material given to him and his
company by other third parties that is
no different than if the New York Times
or CNN or Fox take some they're given a
tip on something that's going on within
the government they talk about it it's
the same exact thing that's metal
be so